Wanatchaporn Churvivat



My Portfolio

C

(+66)099-020-3144



proywanat@gmail.com



github.com/proywanat

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (Computer Science)

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok (2019-2023) GPAX: 2.77

SKILLS

Programming

- CC++
- PostgreSQL SQLite

Web Development

- HTML PHP CSS JavaScript
- React (JavaScript/TypeScript)
- Next.js Redux
- Angular Node.js/Express.js
- Java SpringBoot

Application Development

- Flutter/Java
- Firebase

Data Engineering

• Python SQL

Other

- Git AWS MongoDB
- API Messaging

LANGUAGE

- Thai (Native)
- English

PROFILE

My name is Wanat. I am a Software Developer with 1 year of experience in developing and maintaining web and mobile applications. I have aptitude in various programming languages and frameworks such as ReactJS, Java, and Flutter to deliver the best results that meet user needs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

T-ECOSYS Co.,Ltd.

12/2023 - Current

Software Developer

- Industrial Digital Platform (iDP) Project: Handled website translation, bug fixes with international teams, and feature development using Next.js (TypeScript) and Spring Boot.
- Singhdam Alumni Chulalongkorn University: Assigned to design and develop the alumni association website for Chulalongkorn University using WordPress.
- iDP Ecommerce Project: Tasked with designing an industrial
 e-commerce website using WordPress and develop the
 main iDP website to ensure seamless connectivity between the two
 platforms.

JENOSIZE Co.,Ltd.

07/2023 - 11/2023

Full Stack Engineer

- Marketing Cloud Project: Developed new features based on client needs such as CRM management, Live Chat enhancements, and Automate Flows. Key clients include CP ALL (7-Eleven) and Big C.
- 7Chat&Shop Project: Built an ordering system via LINE for CP ALL (7-Eleven), and collaborated closely on issue resolution with clients and QA.
- Live Chat System (PF Project): Created a property chat system for Property Perfect, including message-counting APIs and push notification setup via OneSignal for iOS and Android.

WORK EXPERIENCE

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

06/2019-04/2023

Bachelor's degree student

- Developed a table reservation system inspired by Chef's Table using Python programming language
- Developed a personal portfolio website using HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Developed an object-oriented programming (OOP) game using Java programming language.
- Developed a Flutter/Firebase jokes application for buying and selling.
- Developed website about parts of a car (JR Autoparts) using HTML/CSS/PHP
- Developed final project a web application for MES (Manufacturing Execution System) using the Ignition Platform for SCG Company Limited.